The solution is that we need to call
Fragment.setHasOptionsMenu(true). That way, we'll
get appropriate options menu callback
methods in the fragment, so that we can
inflate the menu and for when a menu item
is selected. And this is where the fragment
inflates the menu. Remember from before that in the
ForecastFragment class, we have a public empty constructor, and
we also override onCreateView? We also define fetchWeatherTask here.
Now, we're going to overide an additional fragment life
cycle method called onCreate. This is where the fragment
is created, and this happens before the onCreate view
method, which is where the UI gets initialized. So, in
onCreate, we're going to call setHasOptionsMenu to be true to
indicate that we want call backs for these methods.
When onCreateOptionsMenu is called, we're going to inflate the menu
layout that we defined earlier called forecast fragment. We'll also
get notified when a menu item is selected. When a menu item with
ID action refresh is called, we're going to
return true for now. We're going to go
over the activity and fragment life cycle methods in more detail in later
lessons, but if you want, you can read the documentation linked below for now.